# **Cameron French**

Louisville, Kentucky | cameron.french92@gmail.com | 217-416-3887 | www.linkedin.com/in/cameron-french-293779183/ |

Github: github.com/cameronfrench

## **Full Stack Web Developer**

Full Stack Web Developer leveraging over ten years of experience in customer service to create web applications that provide an effortless experience for the user. With a client-first perspective in web development, I have a passion for developing creative yet practical applications that serve the user. I have strengths in problem-solving, team communication, and I am self-motivated.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Vanderbilt University,** Online — Full Stack Web Development Certificate

April 2023 - October 2023

Geoge Fox University, Portland, Oregon— M.A. Intercultural & Indigenous Studies

August 2018 - August 2021

Ozark Christian College, Joplin, MO— B.A. Intercultural Studies

August 2012 - May 2017

#### **EXPERIENCE**

**Pic-Time,** Remote — Customer Success Agent

September 2021 - PRESENT

- Provide chat support by educating users, reporting technical issues, and resolving order complaints.
- Manage 30-50 support tickets daily and work with partners to resolve client requests.
- Help bring down chat response times to 10 minutes.
- Work with our software team to run beta testing and search for bugs in new releases.

#### Cameron French Photography, Louisville, Kentucky— Owner/Photographer

December 2019 - Present

- Oversee and manage multiple clients over an average of 9-month periods.
- Develop annual budgets and catalog and create expense reports.
- In 2021, I doubled my gross income compared to the previous year.
- Designed and created a website to reach a targeted clientele.

### Twin Oaks Christian Church, Woodhaven, MI — Guest Services and Small Groups Director

February 2017 - April 2019

- Implemented a small group strategy, effectively launching over 20 groups within the first three months of starting.
- Developed and trained 20+ group leaders to oversee small groups and provided continue training opportunities.
- Oversaw 30+ volunteers for the guest services team, implemented new materials to capture new visitor information, and developed a post-visit strategy for better retention.
- Designed and created a website that included creating multiple pages, forms, and media content to match branding changes in the church.

## **SKILLS**

JavaScript ES6+, CSS, HTML, GitHub, MySQL, Express, Node, MVC, Handlebars, Bootstrap

## **STRENGTHS**

Problem-Solving, Organization, Customer Experience, Self-Driven, Communication